// Quesitons for Game of Thrones Category
// One object for each question

const gotQuestions = [
   
   {
      "question" : "Who was Jon Snow's father?",
      "correctAns" : "Rhaegar Targaryen",
      "multChoice" : ["Gerold Hightower", "Rhaegar Targaryen", "Robert Baratheon", "Eddard Stark", "Balon Greyjoy"]
   },
   
   {
      "question" : "To which house was Maester Aemon born?",
      "correctAns" : "Targaryen",
      "multChoice" : ["Targaryen", "Tyrell", "Hightower", "Dayne", "Stark"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What was the actual name of the 'Mad King'?",
      "correctAns" : "Aerys II",
      "multChoice" : ["Aegon IV", "Aenys I", "Jaehaerys I", "Viserys II", "Aerys II"]
   },

   

   {
      "question" : "In which town is the Citadel where Maesters train?",
      "correctAns" : "Oldtown",
      "multChoice" : ["Braavos", "Oldtown", "Molestown", "Fairmarket", "White Harbor"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What does a Valyrian Steel link signify on a Maester's chain?",
      "correctAns" : "Higher Mysteries",
      "multChoice" : ["Warcraft", "Medicine", "Ravenry","Higher Mysteries", "Astronomy"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Who did Robb Stark execute for killing the Lannister prisoners?",
      "correctAns" : "Rickard Karstark",
      "multChoice" : ["Wendel Manderly", "Robin Flint", "Donnel Locke", "Smalljon Umber", "Rickard Karstark"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What is the name of the sword of House Dayne?",
      "correctAns" : "Dawn",
      "multChoice" : ["Heartsbane", "Ice", "Dawn", "Dark Sister", "Blackfyre"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Which is not an aspect of The Seven?",
      "correctAns" : "The Child",
      "multChoice" : ["The Stranger", "The Crone", "The Smith", "The Child", "The Warrior"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Where are people infected with Greyscale sent?",
      "correctAns" : "Valyria",
      "multChoice" : ["Valyria", "Braavos", "Astapor", "Lhazar", "Qarth"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What was the name of Aegon the Conqueror's dragon?",
      "correctAns" : "Balerion",
      "multChoice" : ["Seasmoke", "Meraxes", "Dreamfyre", "Balerion", "Vhagar"]
   },

]

export{
   gotQuestions
}